Guide to the Archives of Irish America Vertical File Collection AIA.013
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- I
  - The Irish Ancestral Research Association, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Apostolate in Brooklyn and Queens, 1993-; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Center (An Claidheamh Soluis, Inc.), circa 1972-1998; 2 Folders (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Center: Traditional Dance Festival, 1990-1993; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Center: Traditional Music Festival, 1988-1996; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Festival, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Forum of Rockland County, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Arts Foundation, 1996; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - The Irish Association of Nova Scotia, 1995; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Book Center, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Books and Graphics, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Books and Media, Inc., 1980-1981, 1991-2005, undated; 2 Folders (Box 11)
  - The Irish Bookshop, 1994-2000, undated; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Brigade Association, 1991-; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Bronx Theatre Company, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - Irish Business Organization of New York, 1991-1999; 2 Folders (Box 11)
  - Irish Center Leeds, 1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Civil War, 2010 (Box 22)
  - Irish Communist Organization Pamphlet #7: The Fenians by Karl Marx, 1977; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Irish Connections(Premier Issue), 2000; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Craft and Gift Exhibitors, circa 1998-2001; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Cultural Society (California), 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Cultural Society Foundation (Maryland), 1995-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Cultural Society of Garden City, 1991-; 1 folder (Box 12, 22)
  - Irish Cultural and Sports Centre, Inc., 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Culture Week Committee, Feb 1980; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Diaspora Project, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Directory, 1996-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Echo, 1978-1979, 1994-2000; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Edition, circa 1997; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Emigrant, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Emigrant Vote Campaign, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish and English dictionaries, 1995-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Eyes (Arizona), 1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Family History Events, 1999-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Family History Forum, Inc., 1993-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Famine Curriculum Committee, circa 1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Famine/Genocide Committee, 1996-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Fest (Milwaukee), 1991-1997; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Festival of the Arts (NYC), undated; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Festival of Stars, 1960, 1965; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Film Association (NYC), 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Focus (non-profit group), circa 1993; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Food Distributors, Inc., 1996-1999; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Franciscan Brothers, Apr 1975; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Gazette, Sep 2008; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Genealogical Foundation, 1990-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Genealogical Society, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Georgian Society, Jan 1966-Mar 1966; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Globe: News for Irish Immigrants, Nov 1995 (Box 21)
  - Irish Guide Dogs Association, 1995; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Herald, 1998; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Heritage Society of America, undated; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Hour (Chicago and San Francisco, Mar 1961; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - The Irish Hour, Nov 1953; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial, 1995-2004; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Illustrated (Vol 1, no. 9), Nov 1956; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Immigration Center, 2001-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Immigration Reform Movement, 1989, 2007; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Labor History Society, Dublin, undated (Box 12)
  - Irish Language Courses, 1998-2001; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Language Events, 1983-1997; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Language Schools, 1975-1998; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization, 1993-2000; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Literature, 1971-1979; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Media Image Group, 1983-1986; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish National Caucus, 1983-; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Night at Shea Stadium, 1997, 2000; 1 folder (Box 12)
  - Irish Northern Aid Testimonial, Jan 1987, 1994; 2 Folders (Box 12)
  - Irish Northern Aid and The Irish People: research paper and supporting documentation, 1972-2006 (Box 12)
  - Irish Organizations (various), 1960s- (Box 13)
  - Irish Pavillion (letterhead), undated; 1 folder (Box 22)
  - Irish Pages: A Journal of Contemporary Writing, 2008; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Progressive League (photocopies of originals), 1918, undated (Box 13)
  - The Irish Radio Singers, 1958; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Rebel Music, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The Irish Rebel Theatre, circa 1980; 1 folder, 1 oversize folder (Box 21)
  - The Irish Repertory Theatre (4 folders), 1989-2009; 4 Folders (Box 21)
  - Irish Republican Army (IRA), undated; 1 folder (Box 9)
  - Irish Republican Clubs, USA and Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Irish Roots Magazine, 1992; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Socialist Federation in America, undated (Box 13)
  - Irish Studies: Course Lists/Syllabi, 1988-1996; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Studies Events, Conferences and Lectures, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Studies Programs in Ireland, 1970-2006; 4 Folders (Box 13)
  - Irish Studies Programs in the United States, 1987-2002; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Task Force of the National Lawyer's Guild, 1986; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Teachers' Association, 1974-1983; 2 Folders (Box 13)
  - The Irish Times (On the Web), 1994; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Tourist Board in America, 1978-1998; 2 Folders (Box 13)
  - Irish Trade Board in America, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The Irish Transport and General Workers' Union, 1934; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Irish Travel Agents Association Inc., 1976-1992; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Travel Agents Association of New York, 1979; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Vise, 1995-1997, undated (Box 13)
  - The Irish Voice, 1990s; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The Irish Way (Irish American Cultural Institute), 1992; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Weekends, 1991-1998; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Irish Workers Club of Boston, 1930s (Box 13)
  - Irish World: Centennial celebration, 21 May 1971 (Box 21)
  - Island: Arts from Ireland, May 2000; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Ivers, Eileen, 1996; 1 folder (Box 13)
- J
  - James Joyce Quarterly, undated; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The Jeanie Johnston Project, 1990s; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Jerry McCabe Fellowship Program, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Jersey Shore Irish Festival, 1997; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Jewish Monthly, 2001; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The John McCormack Society of America, Oct 1975; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Jones, Mary Harris, 2001; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Journal of Prisoners on Prisons, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 13)
- K
  - Kells Publishing Company, circa 1994; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963, 1979, 2003; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., II, 1986; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - The Keshcarrigan Bookshop, circa 1980-1987; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - King, Peter, Representative, Long Island, 2010 (Box 13)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1982; 1 folder (Box 13)
- L
  - Labor Unions: Ireland and New York City, 1998; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Ladies of Charity, 1990; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Larkin, Jim, 1915; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - The Lavender and Green Alliance, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Lawe, John E., 1989; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - "Leaving Ireland" by Francis J. Gallagher, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Lecture Series, 2003; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Lectures on Ireland Rebellions (1798, 1848), 1998; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Libraries and Archives, circa 2007-2008; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Linen Hall Library, Belfast, undated; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 2000; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Loyal League of the Yiddish Sons of Erin, 1966-1967, 1984; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Lynch Dance Tour of Ireland, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 13)
- M
  - MacDonagh, Thomas, undated; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Mac Stiofain, Sean, 2001; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Magazine articles - various topics, circa 1971-; 2 Folders (Box 21)
  - Makem, Tommy, 1986; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Malachy McCourt for Governor, 2006; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Manhattan Irish-American Society, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Manning, John B., undated; 1 folder (Box 13)
  - Mayo Foundation for the Handicapped, 1973-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - McCarthy, Joe, 2000; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McCormack, John, 1928; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McCourt, Frank, 1997; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McKenna, Siobhan, 1987; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McKiernan, Eoin, Dr., 1917-2004; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - McSorley's 150 Year Anniversary Calendar, 2004; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Meany, George, 1969; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Melbourne and the Irish Famine, Dec 1998; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Memorials for the Deceased, 1984-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Michael Collins (The Film), 1990-1996; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Mick Moloney's Irish Folklore Tours, 1993-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Mid-Atlantic Irish (Celtic) Directory, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Mid-Atlantic Irish Organizations, undated; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Míle Fáilte Radio Program, circa 1991-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Moakley, Joseph, 2001; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Moloney, Michael (Mick), 1988, 2004; 1 folder, 1 oversize folder (Box 14, 24 (OV))
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1947, 1988, 2000-2004; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Mulvey, Harold M., 2000; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Murphy, Judge Francis T., 1962; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Murphy, Maureen, 2001; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Museum of the City of New York, 1996; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music: Album of Songs by Victor Herbert. M. Witmark and Sons, New York., 1927 (Box 14)
  - Music Clippings, 1988-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music Companies, Producers and Artists, 1992-; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music/Dance Events, 1975-2003; 2 Folders (Box 14)
  - Music Lyrics, undated; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music Lyrics: "More Than 1000 Songs and Dances of the Irish People", 1976; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music Publications, undated; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music Study Programs, circa 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music Tours, 1997; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Music: Traditional, c. 1992; 1 folder (Box 14)
- N
  - National Cathedral of Saint Patrick (Dublin), 2000; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - National Geographic, Apr 1976; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - National Irish Freedom Committee: 14th Annual Michael Flannery Testomionial Awards Dinner, 2009 (Box 14)
  - National Library of Ireland, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - National Museum of Catholic Art and History, 1999; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - National Union for Social Justice (membership application), 1934 (Box 14)
  - New Age Music, 1995; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New Hibernia Review, 1996; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New Ireland Forum, 1983; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - New Irish Works, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York Celtic Colloquium, 1997; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York City District 22: Ethnic Studies Project, 1979; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York Daily News, 1981; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - The New York Genealogical and Biographical Society, 1998; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York H-Block Armagh Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 14)
  - New York Irish Center, 2004-2006; 1 folder (Box 14, 21)
  - New York Irish History Roundtable, 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York Law School Journal of International and Comparative Law, 1990; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York Magazine, 1971, 1976; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - New York Police Department/Fire Department of New York, 2002-2007; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - The New York Trinity Alumni Association, 1997; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York University, 1994-1999; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York World's Fair, 1964; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - New York's Oblong, 1973; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings (General), circa 1970-; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Irish Echo, 1973-2001; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings about Irish Language, 1993-2001; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: New York Post, 1972-2003; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: New York Times (2 folders), circa 1972 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Small and Local Papers, 1963-2002; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - The Next Wave (Radio), undated; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - Noon, Paddy, 1985; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - North American Association for Celtic Language Teachers, 1994-2000; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - North American Buyers Association Inc., 1992-1996; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - North American Celtic Buyers Association, 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 14)
  - North American Distribution of Irish and Low Budget European Tours, 1995; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Northern Ireland, 1969-1972, 2000 (Box 21)
  - Notre Dame Keough Institute of Irish Studies, 2001; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Nuacht a hAon, 1995; 1 folder (Box 15)
- O
  - Oatlands Celtic Festival, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Brien, J. Kenneth, 1996; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Observer Magazine, 1988; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - The O'Casey Theater Company, 1982, 1993; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - O'Connell, Emmett, 1936; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Connor, Cardinal John, 2000; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Connor's Fairways Travel, Inc., 1992; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1963-1998; 1 folder, 1 oversize folder (Box 15, 24 (OV))
  - O'Dwyer, William, 1948, 1964; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Faolain, Nuala, 2001; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Office of the Council President, City of New York, undated; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Hara, Maureen, Feb 1987; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Malley, Ernie, 1991-1998 (Box 15)
  - O'Neill, Eugene, Aug 1986; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Neill, Thomas "Tip", 1986; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Orange Marches/Nationalist Resistance, 2004-; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - O'Reilly, Gerald, 1990 (Box 15)
  - O'Sullivan, Maureen, 1989; 1 folder (Box 15)
- P
  - Paddyology, 1992; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Parish of Saint Ann, 1981; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - The Pearse Commemoration Committee of New York, 1979; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Pelican Publishing Company, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Penguin Putnam Inc., 1994; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group's Annual Traditional Irish Music & Dance Festival, 1993-1999; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia Immigration Resource Center, 2001; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Photography Exhibitions, undated, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Pittsburgh Irish Festival, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Plain Truth Ministries, 1982; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Pluto Press, 1987; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Poetry, 1976, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Political Education Committee, 1995; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Political/Radical Publications, 1977; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Politics: Irish, undated; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Politics: Irish American, 1978; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Postcards, 1996; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Project Irish Outreach, 1990; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: Canada, 2004; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: Ireland, 1995-1999; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United Kingdom, 1992; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (A-H), circa 1975-2001; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (I-Q), 1977-2004; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Publishers: United States (R-U), circa 1981-2001; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Pubs/Bars and Restaurants, 1980-; 1 folder (Box 15)
- Q
  - Queensland Irish Association, 1948, 1973; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Quinn, Carmel, 1957, 1999; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Quinn, D.P., undated; 1 folder (Box 15)
- R
  - Radio Specials of Irish Interest, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Recording Labels, 1963-; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Regent Graphics, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Rego Irish Records, 1980-; 2 Folders (Box 15)
  - Republican Sinn Fein, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Rising Labor Commonwealths, 1918; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Riverdance, 1996-; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Roberts Rinehart Publishers, 1994-1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Robinson, Mary, Oct 1997; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Rosalind Walshe Collection, 1999; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Rose of Tralee Metropolitan New York Committee, 1977, 1992-; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Royal Irish Academy, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 16)
- S
  - Saint Brendan's Annual Irish Day Parade and Festival, 1992; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Brendan - Voyage, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Saint Brigid's Church, 2006; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Jerome's Church, 1943, undated; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Martin's Press, 1990-2002; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Mary's University, 1995-1999; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Fathers: Annual Dance, May 1968; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Brooklyn, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Quad Cities, 1997; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick Society of Queens, 2002; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Cathedral, 1942-; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day, 1977-; 2 Folders (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Cards, undated; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Celebration: Ticonderoga, NY, 1866 (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day: New York City Ball, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 16)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Brooklyn Irish American Parade Committee, Inc., 1977, 1987-2006; 6 Folders (Box 16-17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee, 1971-2004; 6 Folders (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee Scholarship, 1991; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee Line of March, undated; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee: Arizona, 1995; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, West Orange (program), Mar 14, 2010 (Box 21)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Emmetsburg Saint Patrick's Association, 1991; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade, Inc., 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Mineola Irish-American Society of Nassau, Suffolk, and Queens, Inc., 1976, 1987-2004; 3 Folders (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Mid-Hudson Saint Patrick's Day Parade, 2000; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parades: New York City, 1999-2000; 2 Folders (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parades: New York City (program), 2009 (Box 21)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Newark Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, Inc., 1994; 1 folder (Box 17)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Nutley Irish-American Association, 2004; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Queens County Saint Patrick's Day Parade and Cultural Committee, 1995-2005; 4 Folders (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Syracuse Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Tarrytown and Sleepy Hollow Saint Patrick's Day Parade, 2001; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: WPIX, Mar 1978; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade: Yonkers Saint Patrick's Day Parade Committee, 1986; 2 Folders (Box 18)
  - Saint Patrick's Old Cathedral, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Saint Rita's Parish, 1950; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sanger, Margaret Higgins, 1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Scanlon, John, 2001; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Scoil Gaeilge Ghearóid Tóibín, 1993-1998; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Scoil Gaeilge Mhichil uí Locháín, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Scottish Lion Import Shop, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - The Searing-Roslyn United Methodist Church, 1996-2001; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sectarianism on Parade, 2005; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - "A Sense of Ireland" (publication), 1980; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - The Shamrock Ballroom, circa 1950; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Shamrock Gift Shop, undated; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - The Shanachie (Connecticut Irish American Historical Society), 1994; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Shanachie Records Corporation, 1977-1997; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Shannon Duty Free Shopping, 1997-; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sheridan, General Philip H., 1985; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Shriver, Maria, Aug 2000; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sinn Fein, 1906, 1981, undated (Box 18)
  - The Sixth Annual International Theatre Festival, 1991; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Slieve Bawn Handcraft Co-operative Supporters, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Smith, Captain James, 1986; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Social Democratic and Labour Party, May 2002; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick - Westchester County, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Songs of the Irish Union Soldier, 1861-1865, 1998; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1956-; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sporting Events, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Spudchucker Collective, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - The Stone Street Press, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Stylus Publishing, 1998-2001; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Sullivan, Ed, undated; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Syracuse University Press, circa 1998; 1 folder (Box 18)
- T
  - Tara Circle, 1992-; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Teilifis na Gaeilge (Network Ireland Television), undated; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Television: Irish and Irish American Roles, 1998; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Television Programs of Irish Interest, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Tereshchuk, David, 2001; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Theater, 1946-2007; 13 folders
    - Broadway Productions: A-C, 1982-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Productions: D-F, 1982-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Productions: H-M, 1981-2000; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Productions: P-S, 1966-2007; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Productions: T-U, 1995-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Productions: W, 1988-1999; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - Broadway Reviews, 1963-; 1 folder (Box 19)
    - Off-Broadway Productions: G-M, 1946-1992; 1 folder (Box 19)
    - Off-Broadway Productions: O-W, 1946-2004; 1 folder (Box 19)
    - Off-Off-Broadway, 1988-1998; 3 Folders (Box 19)
    - Small Productions, 1975-; 1 folder, 1 oversize folder (Box 19)
  - Theatre Omnibus, 1996-; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Thomas Davis Irish Players, 1982, 1995; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Thornton, John J., 1990; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Tom Geraghty Association, 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Tommy Makem's Irish Pavillion, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Trade Exhibitions, 1992-1998; 2 Folders (Box 19)
  - The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, Inc., May 1973; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Travel Brochures, 1958-1980; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Trinity College: The Book of Kells Collection, 1995; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - Tuxedo Ballroom, 1960; 1 folder (Box 19)
- U
  - U2, 1987; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - "Ulysses in Hand: The Rosenbach Manuscript", 2000; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - United Arts Club Limited, Dec 1980; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Irish American Studies Committee, 1988, 1997; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - United Irish American Immigration Committee, circa 1986; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - United Irish American Societies of the Delaware Valley, 1988; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, 1987; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - University College Cork, 1992-1997; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - University College Dublin, undated; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - University College Dublin in North America, 1985-1997; 1 folder (Box 19)
  - University of Notre Dame, circa 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - University of St. Thomas, 1997; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - U.S.-Ireland Alliance, 2000; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - U.S. Irish (Publication), undated; 1 folder (Box 20)
- V
  - Veterans Corps 69th Infantry Regiment, 1974, 1992-1997; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Villanova University, 1993; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - The Vinegar Hill History and Preservation League, 1998; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - "The Voice of Ireland", 1990s; 1 folder (Box 20)
- W
  - Wake Forest University Press, 1994-; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Wallace, Mike, undated; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - W.B. Yeats Drama Foundation, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - W.B. Yeats Society of New York, 1991-; 1 folder (Box 20)